[Music]
why investing in messaging and video
that the megatrends will make you a
better marketer let's dive in and study
more about it consider these statistics
the world's top four messaging apps
whatsapp Facebook messenger WeChat and
viber now have a combined total of
nearly 4 billion monthly active users
that's more than the combined total of
the top 4 social networks Facebook
Instagram Twitter and LinkedIn it's
predicted that by the end of this year
more than three-quarters seventy six
point three percent of the world's
smartphone users will be regularly using
messaging apps meanwhile 10 billion
videos are now being watched on snapchat
every single day 100 million hours of
video are being watched on Facebook per
day it's predicted that by 2021 video
traffic will account for 82 percent of
all Internet traffic
[Music]
these are just a few of the reasons why
at code carat we consider a messaging
and video to be megatrends they are not
just popular marketing channels they're
gaeta ways for reaching billions of
potential customers all around the world
[Music]
after analyzing the marketing tools
being used by all 100 companies on
forbes cloud 100 lists we discovered
that 15% of them are using messaging on
their websites of the 15 companies with
messaging on their sites 9 display it on
every page of their site while the other
six target specific pages or types of
pages of those 15 companies using
messaging 10 use welcome messages to
greet visitors and of those 10 companies
using welcome messages to are using a
virtual assistant to engage with leads
overall we found that 69% of cloud 100
companies have a call to action CTA on
their website that prompts people to get
in touch with sales however only two of
those companies give you the opportunity
to chat with someone live after clicking
that CTA by replacing your contact us
form with messaging or simply by adding
live chat on your site you can generate
more leads and ultimately shorten your
sales cycle during our research for the
cloud 100 report we found that 34% of
cloud 100 companies are producing video
content on a regular basis we defined
regular basis as having uploaded fresh
video content at least once for a month
over the past few months of those 34
companies producing videos regularly all
of them upload their videos to YouTube
20 upload their videos to facebook and 5
upload their videos to Vimeo overall
adoption of video is more widespread
among the
loud 100 compared to messaging adoption
with just over one-third of companies
producing video content on a regular
basis and while YouTube is clearly the
most popular channel for uploading video
content it's noteworthy that one fifth
of cloud 100 companies are regularly
uploading video directly to Facebook and
not just sharing links to video content
uploaded to YouTube remember that stat
from earlier 100 million hours of video
are now being watched on Facebook per
day one quick note about Vimeo while
just 5 cloud 100 companies have uploaded
video content there in the past month 17
companies use the service overall and
that makes it one of the top 25 most
views tools by the cloud 100 the
difference is that instead of using
Vimeo as a social network for sharing
new videos regularly most use it as a
way to host their evergreen videos like
product walkthrough videos on their
websites while at first glance they
might seem like completely unrelated
technologies messaging on video both
deliver and on demand personalized
experience that buyers have come to
expect these days and while messaging
lets you engage with visitors in real
time on your site video can help you
drive those visitors there in the first
place
what messaging does for personalized
one-to-one outreach on your website
video can do for your outbound emails
successful be DRS are using personalized
video instead of voice mails and driving
higher engagement and click throughs on
their emails because of it what
messaging can do for your website video
can be for your outreach and the combo
of the two is unstoppable want a
successful project with code carrot
visit www.qcnet.com
[Music]